<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dusit Thani on Tech Jaunts</title>
    <link>https://adarshnair.online/hugo_blog/tags/dusit-thani/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dusit Thani on Tech Jaunts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ribice&#34;&gt;Emir Ribic&lt;/a&gt; 2017</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://adarshnair.online/hugo_blog/tags/dusit-thani/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Memorable Stay at Dusit Thani Dubai: My Birthday Surprise</title>
      <link>https://adarshnair.online/hugo_blog/post/dubai_trip_dusit_thani/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adarshnair.online/hugo_blog/post/dubai_trip_dusit_thani/</guid>
      <description>My wife and I recently took a trip to Dubai for my birthday, and we had the pleasure of staying at the Dusit Thani Dubai. From the moment we arrived, the experience was nothing short of amazing.
We had booked the hotel in advance, and my wife had made a special request for a birthday cake to be arranged for me. To our surprise, when we arrived at the hotel, a delicious cake was waiting for us in our room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dubai diaries: From flight to hotel and everything in between</title>
      <link>https://adarshnair.online/hugo_blog/post/trip_to_dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adarshnair.online/hugo_blog/post/trip_to_dubai/</guid>
      <description>Before departing on our trip, we made sure to obtain a visa for entry into Dubai. The process of obtaining a visa online was quick and easy. All we needed was a valid passport and a credit card to pay the visa fee. We got our visa from MakeMyTrip which was very convenient and fast. The visa was issued electronically and we received it within a few days. With this visa, we were able to travel not only to Dubai, but also to other cities within the United Arab Emirates, such as Abu Dhabi and Sharjah.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>